<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>raggebatman</title>
    <subtitle>Hi, I'm Ragge. I tend to this feed sporadically and chaotically. Enter with caution (cue evil laughter)</subtitle>
    <link href="https://ragge.gay/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://ragge.gay/" />
    <id>tag:ragge.gay,2023:feed.xml</id>
    <author>
        <name>Ragge</name>
        <email>me@ragge.gay</email>
    </author>
    <updated>2023-11-07T13:20:00+01:00</updated>
    <entry>
        <title>Small note about static IP adressing on Debian</title>
        <id>tag:ragge.gay,2023-11-22:small-note-about-static-ip-adressing-on-debian</id>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
        <published>2023-11-22T00:00:00+01:00</published>
        <content>
        Something I found out recently is that the DHCP client
        doesn't get configured correctly on Debian if you edit
        the /etc/network/interfaces file to set a static address
        before bringing the interface down.

        What happens instead is that you set a static address...
        and then the interface gets reconfigured with a dynamic
        address after a while. You actually need to bring the
        interface down (using ifdown) while the file is configured
        for DHCP addressing in order for the DHCP client to be
        disabled.

        So, if you're setting a static address, don't be like
        me and instead remember to bring the interface down before
        configuring it :)

        Interestingly, the wiki page simply states to "disable
        all DHCP services" when you're setting a static address
        which admittedly is all well and true which I forgot to
        do- but never is there a mention that this is done for
        you if you do it this way! As long as you're using the
        DHCP client provided by the installer of course.
        </content>
        <category term="linux" />
        <category term="networking" />
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is AV programming?</title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="/feed/what-is-av-programming" />
        <id>tag:ragge.gay,2023-11-13:what-is-av-programming</id>
        <updated>2023-11-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
        <published>2023-11-13T00:00:00+01:00</published>
        <summary>Short introduction to the coding world of the audiovisual.</summary>
        <category term="programming" />
        <category term="audiovisual" />
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The journey of my website</title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="/feed/the-journey-of-my-website" />
        <id>tag:ragge.gay,2023-11-06:the-journey-of-my-website</id>
        <updated>2023-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
        <published>2023-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</published>
        <summary>Thought I'd let you in on some trivia regarding this place.</summary>
        <category term="meta" />
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <id>tag:ragge.gay,2023-11-02:hello-world</id>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
        <published>2023-11-02T00:00:00+01:00</published>
        <content>Hi all! This is the first entry of my feed. Not quite sure what will become of this... only time will tell!</content>
        <category term="meta" />
    </entry>
</feed>